const mongoose = require('mongoose');
require('./db.js');
const Card = require('../models/card.js');

const entries = [
  {
    theme: 'Столицы',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Стола Канады?',
        price: 100,
        variants: ['Торонто', 'Мельбурн', 'Оттава'],
        correct: 'Оттава',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица Великобритании?',
        price: 200,
        variants: ['Прага', 'Воронеж', 'Лондон'],
        correct: 'Лондон',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица США?',
        price: 300,
        variants: ['Лондон', 'Вашингтон', 'Париж'],
        correct: 'Вашингтон',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица России?',
        price: 400,
        variants: ['Лондон', 'Москва', 'Париж'],
        correct: 'Москва',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица Египта?',
        price: 500,
        variants: ['Лондон', 'Каир', 'Париж'],
        correct: 'Каир',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    theme: 'Столицы',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Столица Мексики?',
        price: 100,
        variants: ['Пекин', 'Мехико', 'Краснодар'],
        correct: 'Мехико',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица Японии?',
        price: 200,
        variants: ['Лондон', 'Токио', 'Стамбул'],
        correct: 'Токио',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица Португалии?',
        price: 300,
        variants: ['Лондон', 'Лисабон', 'Париж'],
        correct: 'Лисабон',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица Испании?',
        price: 400,
        variants: ['Мадрид', 'Вашингтон', 'Париж'],
        correct: 'Мадрид',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица Китая?',
        price: 500,
        variants: ['Лондон', 'Вашингтон', 'Пекин'],
        correct: 'Пекин',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    theme: 'Столицы',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Столица Мексики?',
        price: 100,
        variants: ['Пекин', 'Мехико', 'Краснодар'],
        correct: 'Мехико',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица Японии?',
        price: 200,
        variants: ['Лондон', 'Токио', 'Стамбул'],
        correct: 'Токио',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица Португалии?',
        price: 300,
        variants: ['Лондон', 'Лиссабон', 'Париж'],
        correct: 'Лиссабон',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица Испании?',
        price: 400,
        variants: ['Мадрид', 'Вашингтон', 'Париж'],
        correct: 'Мадрид',
      },
      {
        question: 'Столица Китая?',
        price: 500,
        variants: ['Лондон', 'Вашингтон', 'Пекин'],
        correct: 'Пекин',
      },
    ],
  },
];

(async () => {
  await mongoose.connection.dropDatabase();
  await Card.insertMany(entries);
  await mongoose.connection.close(); // or await mongoose.disconnect();
})();
